ledsupermall.com 2015-05-20

# Privacy Policy

**"Your information provided is strictly limited for use within , we DO NOT share customer information with any third party company."**

Information we collect and how we use it
    In order to provide our services, your personal information, such as address is required. Also, we may as well collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide**  \- When you sign up for an Account , we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). Your information provided is strictly limited for use within , we DO NOT share customer information with any third party company.
  * **Cookies**  \- When you visit , we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how customer interactive with user interface.
  * **Log information**  \- When you access our services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * **Customer communications**  \- When you send email or other communications to , we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
  * **Links**  \- may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the customer experience.

      only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our services, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;
  * Protecting the rights or property of  or our users; and
  * Developing new services.

* * *

Information security
    We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
    We restrict access to personal information to  employees in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

* * *

Data integrity
      processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

* * *

Changes to this Privacy Policy
    Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
